let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which is the last book in Gulliver's Travels?",
    answer: "Voyage to Houyhnhnms",
    options: [
      "Voyage to Brobdingnag",
      "Voyage to Balnibarbi",
      "Voyage to Lilliput",
      "Voyage to Houyhnhnms"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which British novelist created the iconic character James Bond?",
    answer: "Ian Fleming",
    options: [
      "Ian Fleming",
      "Alan Moore",
      "Agatha Christie",
      "J. R. R. Tolkien"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which novel by Charles Dickens tells the story of the Jarndyce family?",
    answer: "Bleak House",
    options: [
      "David Copperfield",
      "Bleak House",
      "Little Dorrit",
      "Hard Times"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who completed Christopher Marlowe’s poem Hero and Leander?",
    answer: "George Chapman",
    options: [
      "George Chapman",
      "Ben Jonson",
      "Michael Drayton",
      "John Marston"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Who wrote the epic poem The Divine Comedy?",
    answer: "Dante",
    options: [
      "Giovanni Boccaccio",
      "Ludovico Ariosto",
      "Dante",
      "Henry of Settimello"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who is regarded as the father of the English novel?",
    answer: "Henry Fielding",
    options: [
      "Wilkie Collins",
      "Henry Fielding",
      "Thomas Hardy",
      "William Makepeace Thackeray"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "To which country does the Njáls saga and the Gísla saga belong?",
    answer: "Iceland",
    options: [
      "Iceland",
      "Poland",
      "Hungary",
      "Austria"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who wrote the epic poems Paradise Lost and Paradise Regained?",
    answer: "John Milton",
    options: [
      "T. S. Eliot",
      "John Milton",
      "William Wordsworth",
      "John Donne"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which work by Ovid is a collection of mythological stories?",
    answer: "Metamorphoses",
    options: [
      "Amores",
      "Tristia",
      "Ars Amatoria",
      "Metamorphoses"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who is the author of The Spirit of Laws?",
    answer: "Montesquieu",
    options: [
      "Voltaire",
      "Montesquieu",
      "Jean-Jacques Rousseau",
      "Immanuel Kant"
    ]
  },
];

